All rights.
I think we're just going to get...started thank you very much for coming to this
...how the stashing I hope everyone enjoyed itthe wonderful key
notes I was really incredible key notes in a very long as well
...hope you really enjoy all the demos and exciting progress there I
...conference allies really fall microsoft developers...in this breakouts
meshing my colleague ryan and I have a chance to tell you the
...exciting stuff and a tools and api is
...case we actually booting to
apps the smarts to the data and...apps your building.
This is a title inv de file talk as I mentioned the...and I would
do this presentation together just a friendly reminder that's
...we really, really want to get your feedback for every stashing
every presentation we do...end of this presentation...would be great if you can some
made the evaluation and please say rein did a good job.
So, we are going to talk about
something called the project oxford's it's really,
really very...
Fall what...we actually can really do in terms of adding smarts to the
...that applications you have.
Specifically what we're going to show you today is a
portfolio of rest api some is the case that
will help you to write applications when you deal with this massive amount of
...especially the kind of multimedia data from speech voice
to...image...to text how can you actually
understands what's going on with the
content you have the multimedia data and how can you make some sense out of the...
As many of you aware and the recently is
...so much...the explosive growth of online...and a lot of us
in that can get access to...few butte apps.
...you really care about all this mobile devices now
just everywhere and everyone in every device is collecting law
...than anyone connection make sense out of that if you think that the positively
you can...those data together and the think abouts in the between p hold data
...all those things you might be able to figure out the relationship in
...yet this morning mention abouts you could think about the kind of graph.
Butts the fundamental problem is really you know-how much we can actually even
null abouts the kind of data there I want to be very clear ways
you that's, you know, the as we think about all this kind of
machine learning kind of problems that we can actually solve.
The different ways to think about that.
We actually view the provi microsoft called the geo machine learning in fact
...tamar my colleague...of zero shall we talk about the greed details I
...keno the tamar of what kind of machine learning...
we can do you can even imagine...project oxford's can be part
of the overall machine learning tools...microsoft would provide
...and what we really want to talk about here is
actually all kind of multimedia data as I mentioned that
...do image attacks what kind of things we can actually do?
I want to get even more specifically
the kind of data that we actually deal with.
The first kind of data is actually vision was all kind of the image in the video
seeing what we can really do.
I actually started the my own the research career
...doing computer vision stuff.
You imagine adding a fifty years ago marvin minsky mit just said
...they just connect camera...gr computer
...computed tell you what the computer really understands so things has really,
really progress a...over the years
especially last five years computer vision has really advanced the...
And, the similarly off-course of
...speech which I also mention very quickly I think significant reason for
...recently I would say that probably qone is just there's just so much more
...secondly I would say allow the machine learning algorithms particularly
deep learning are making huge difference the second set
of things we want to talk about today is actually about a face.
And, if you look at the face and
...you could view that as the specific part of the images but
there's just so special that the so many things you can actually do...the
...recognition...id detection...other things the third...is speech.
I still...twenty-some years ago in a speech was very
...and that was around the time that
...hidden markov models started to really show the promise.
And, if you look at if you plot is all the
error rates over the years in the speech recognition error rates...coming down.
...really took a lot of years that's in the roughly about twenty years ago it was good
...age for speech recognition...speech recognition rate.
Really went down significantly but then there was about ten fifteen years of time that
the speech was not really making too much pairwise their last five years that we once
again the...the unbelievable improvement of speech.
...we get into...point that's the speech recognition is becoming
mainstream is becoming useful and we have had a number of years of...
investments you microsoft is something that I feel very excited about what we can actually often
...to the users and developers I...search should say.
The last one we talk we talk about today is perhaps the thing
I feel most excited about is actually about language understanding it's greedy to
...the phrases in the...speech.
When you put those together?
And, the language understanding a is very difficult.
As you some of you...node that's microsoft recently
announced that described translator where you we actually have
machine translation the started the from the speech then you have some
natural language understanding then you need to have the context you put those in together so today
we will show you a teaser of what's really interesting you can do in
a by actually trini all natural language understanding model in particular
using something called active learning was small amount of data that you starts...
there so runaway tail you a lot of those no details there.
So, you might ask say, you know, why now, you know,
why microsoft's what because we actually have really been
...all kind of machine learning
...fault all kind of multimedia data for long
long-time we actually started speech recognition group in a twenty three years ago study vision group
...years ago you microsoft research and we have trina tons of
different models not only for research projects but also for various products,
products like a being click on a...office?
So, we realize the couple of things one is that's even at the
microsoft's we cannot really require every developer to be machine learning
Secondly we also realize that's in a many difference companies
many different research institutes coming...was very interesting
advanced algorithms for vision visual recognition
...visual understanding speech and all those things
...use really important that we make those advanced
...algorithms...the prototypes and
...available to a large ecosystem
as people continue to contributed to those algorithms such that's
...we can actually share with everyone and the now we can boots
interesting apps not only for windows but across all kind of ecosystems
...heard from...here this morning so that's why we started this
project oxford's not too long ago and we starts.
...a set of in a web services rest api
...such that inuit anywhere...the boots, you know,
we can actually help you to start aways yes
make no mistake we want you have the...the binding of this kind of web
services with all kind of clients and hopefully
we'll be able to continue to deliver is kind of value to you.
Is what talk talking about the developers
a key requirements for any kind of api design...this st case is really
easy to use...we keep this very much in our minds as we
...designing this whole thing my joke to the team is that you just have
to designs the whole api systems so simple?
That even microsoft executives can use it so I'm going
to personally demonstrates show you a demo that actually I wrote the felines of
...and...on this enjoy
a phone in io show you a demo...switches display first.
Great I'll see you can actually see that so it's actually really
fun demo and I just give you a little bit of context and you know, a little bit of marketing each by the
bear with me so my boss the ceo of microsoft's
and the site here is actually a...cricket fan so he actually follows
...those someexciting...gains...like...unfortunately I actually don't know anything about it
and I spend too much time watching american football I guess so.
I have tech knowledge and the we have project author we have all those visual recognition
and the speech and other things so
...media is...the very simple app using this kind of api is so
he's app let me show you a demo here so I can start this and the.
Try to recognize in a couple of not all
...the clears and the which I actually care about because I
...idea follows those guys so if I
just the input a picture let's say I watch tv and the game is going I
...the photo and the from that that's I actually have a picture
of some people actually players playing but I really don't know those guys but
I can submits this picture to the kind of web services that are
butte using project oxford's api
is and I submit that's so now this picture is actually going there as you can
see very quickly and those two people identify...and the
...the names again I want to tell you that those two names
that amount a group of names that actually I wanted the system to recognize so this
mi actually once, you know,...abouts the
...so what I'm going to do is actually now I connectivity reads chewed the
...search engine so now is actually senses being search engine
what's different here is that I actually enhances the being search result with
another set off api services powered by project...that is actually
speech so let me see if you that works here you probably see these that this
...symbol years I presses so I just want to know more about...so.
How old is he?
Was pretty good he's only twenty six while he's doing really well maybe even as a try.
Where was he born?
All rights so you can imagine ads in a wes this kind of web services
...here and you can do a lot of interesting interactions so again adding
the point is that in a how can we really think about to note offering this set of api from speech
to vision to phase to language so that we can help you
use a developers to add the smarts.
To the beta and the application attributing so we
that I'm going to invite the ryan to come up to tell you a lot of the glorious details.
...so my name's...gaussian...program manager in technology
and research I'll tell you a little bit more about the services that we're announcing today with project
oxford.
So, first off as we come back to
...mentioning earlier about how ease of ease of use and how that was kind of a guiding principle
...services so as we built these api is against harris joke about
so easy...even microsoft executive can use it things like detection and identification
very complicated models in the back and very hard to do but we just two lines of code we
have one-line protection one-line to identify it very easy to include these
and any application let me talk a bit more about which services...talking about today?
So, within vision we have...services that you can
...recognized the contents of images we also
...you identify words within those images and finally we
...you generate thumbnails I keep more of the content within your cropped photos.
Base api is a complex and specialized set of tasks within vision we
...of rest api is that you cannot only detect faces you can described
...even predict some features about the spaces but we also...you take a set
of photos that you've never-seen-before you've never label and will group them around the people that are
in those photos and finally we provide the set of tools that you can do identification task that
...has application?
With the speech services we are provide you the ability to both here
users and talk with your users speech recognition you can convert audio into
taxed with the text-to-speech you can easily generate audio files to
speak back to your users all with across multiple languages and finally
...touch on the band was helps you really understand the
intent behind words and behind phrases you can understand only what...of actions you
want to take you can also say what topics you'd like to take those actions on
...the our of active learning was makes it easy for you to get a model
...post-it and building your application around that.
So, first with a vision api as.
We've built in collaboration with the bing team and these help you make
the most of your images and understand what's happening inside of them so the
analyze image service provides a set of features that describe
...and is built specifically with the bing
the image search team so on the left-hand side of the screen you can see input
photo with just this photo input into the analyze image rest api
service we can start to describe what type of images this is a photograph is it in
...color is animated it align drawing...clip art things like that?
Content is what we're really drawing on beings image understanding
so the first item you'll see there is categories so given just this photo of aman
swimming we can return back and say well it really looks like this is someone swimming
so whether or not or whatever the photo into being we can tell you there's a city scape there's cars
there's a cap is a dog we can help you describe the image with only the images the input we have a
...of scores around adult content you can understand if there's pornographic content within
a photograph this can be very useful doing some sort of content moderation and
finally faces which makes use of the face api...which...talk about in more detail later on
what you understand you know-how many faces are and photo as well as predicting
agent even the gender and the location of where that faces found within the photo.
The final set of features on mention from the analyze image service are colors.
So, we can describe this service what are the dominant colors in the front of the image in the back of the
image we can also tell you the accent color that would work best with the images
so by knowing this color information about an image you can make it look beautiful
within your application without having to do a bunch of custom work for each individual photo.
The object character recognition service once you identify and recognize words within
a photo so with this example on the left-hand side this is the only input into
the rest service and not only
doesn't recognize the total text within the photo and where the line
breaks are but it can also predict what language the seems to be
what orientation the words exist in...give you a bounding boxy you can
recognize within the photo where each of the individual words ends up being?
With the smart thumbnail service
often have a need to crop or scale photos but when you do
that it can be challenging to make sure the important content remain center of the frame.
On the left-hand side you can see two sets
of input images and on the right-hand side you can see multiple different cropping is
for these images so right now you can see that the dominant object
and both of those photos can sometimes be lost.
Especially in the right most side we have kind of the most
...cropping going on so when we run these photos to the
smartkom now service.
Switch to hear it keeps more of the content within the frame.
...go back just to show that again so here which is kind of
a naive cropping we start losing some of the some of the content
and the photos especially if you look at the right most items but through the service
...shift and keep that front-and-center this can be
really helpful when you're trying to put photos and multiple spots in your application.
With the face api is this is a set of computer vision tasks
...be recognize human faces within images.
So, the first...talk about is just detection is one of
the core calls that a lot of the otherfeatures face api built on top of so
here given input image example you can see on the left we get
the output...jason object on the right
...first detection looks for one or more faces within a photograph...only does
a detect that face and tell you how many found where within the photo that faces
bound but even tells,... what is the pos
...the person looking it also predicts things like
age predicts things like gender so these are sort of experimental features that
...surfacing with the face api...but, these evolve over time
improve over time finally it gives you set...facial landmarks so the visual
...you can tell where the eyes are where the noses left
...mouth right...the math you can...of all these points across the detected faces?
If I switch over to verification,
verification built on top of detection
with verification you give to input images detect spaces and
...compares the to see whether or not they're likely to be the same person in gives you back...confidence score for that.
Grouping...to build on top of detection and the grouping api
call takes in a set of images in returns back
those images clustered around the detected face within those photos with
no extra information...kind of the start to being able to tag collections of photos.
Moving on to identification, identification is a slightly more complicated
task we provide a separate has that makes...easy to build within
to your application so the first thing you'll do if you want to start identifying faces within a photo
...group of a person group so in this example...that
Then for each person group you can go and you can add one or more person
objects you can describe what that object is so in this case at one of my colleagues
...now when we go back to the detection call that we talked about earlier
at the end of that...given the opportunity to basically ad that face to
in existing person object so overtime with a couple of detection calls you can
build-up a set of example faces for each of the person objects in your group.
Then you can make the identify call where you take a new unlabeled photo capacity
and exist against your existing person group and it will tell you which
person object is this most likely to be or if it doesn't match for any of them will tell you that
it's an unknown base.
So, let me switch over to the speech api
as and talk about how we can help you understand the content of audio.
Speech api is powered by bing we provide to main services the
first voice recognition which converts speech.
And, spoken audio into a string.
...output so you can specify what type of audio file you'd like to generate.
With voice recognition impasse an audio stream or file...you get back a set of
texturing...same back...the
...autonomous great speech recognition and at
...announcing this was support for multiple different languages.
With voice recognition there's two main...at this works in a short form and along for
...short form is really when you think users are going to be issuing single
sentences you know, little fifteen seconds or...kind of utterances
to your application and you can see example on the bottom of the screen so if the input to
this was four hundred fifty sixth street san-francisco short form service
returns back and says well here's a bunch of translations it'll even come back and say, you know,
there might be multiple translations for this or multiple transcriptions for this so here are
...the five most likely ones in one form...this can deal with audio files up to two minutes
...length.
And, it returns back strings at each identified
sentence pause from the service now in both of these examples you can also make use of
a called partial results when you call the service you can tell it instead of just giving me
the final result as you're in the middle of processing this audio file give-me
results along the way.
As...you access the voice recognition service
...to main ways to do this with project oxford the first is a set
...api as and the second is of client
...for windows desktop android and ios both get access to the
same back-end but the primary difference you'll notice between the rest api and the
client library service is that we use the client library this enables you to do
the long form audio processing in addition the client library is what enables
this partial results to come back and this is because the client libraries making use of a
web socket connection so can keep streaming those results back as...making progress on them
and also talk briefly about windows ten which has a set of speech api...speech api is in windows
ten provide a and even further enrich set of speech features things like
voice activation or dealing with microphone array processing or extensible
grammar control specific cheer voice recognition needs.
So, these three different ways of accessing the voice recognition services is really up to
you the developers as to what best fits your application what's best fits
your needs for what features you need support and on the
project oxford website we end up having sample code...some descriptions
...a bit more detail as to the differences between these three different ways of doing voice recognition.
Voice output what-you actually now talk to your users so you can generate files fifteen
seconds in length and has multiple languages that...seventeen actually
...launch and across the seventeen languages many of them have both male
and female voices so depending what type of audio you like to send your users you
can pick that along the bottom of history and if this continues with...ease of
use description so all I have to do when I call the voice output service
...the language I'd like I pick which voice I'd like to use and then they just pass in
the string and it returns back...audio file so let me quickly switch to the
project oxford website and I'll show you an example of these two services?
To first off have...speech detects service here.
Happy to be and build in san francisco.
Listening
...the text and as it was going you can see that the words were adjusting
and shifting themselves over time that's the partial results at work.
Similarly with text-to-speech.
In type in the
text that we'd like to have and then even see that in this case
always specified call is that the language english
and we'd like to use this voice.
And, we have...and welcome to...
Great very easy to start having
dialogue for users with audio and understanding what they're saying.
And, now like to switch to...which stands
for language understanding intelligence service really excited to show you how
...can bring natural language processing injure applications.
just as voice recognition was able to convert audio into taxed
you convert that text into a set of structured understandings
so-you can take this phrase like news about flight delays and you can get back
...response on the right that ends up saying you're not only is
find news the most blakely intent.
But, the topic that we want to operate on...delays.
So, with...you can build this type of model for yourself if
you're application by providing just a few examples with labels so now let me switch
the browser and I'll show you how easy it is...end of actually building a...model.
The first off.
At launch who is going to be in private...
Sign-out this is the page you'll see when you visit the lou's website.
And, first off as a private preview means we're not letting everyone into the
siteat first so you come in and you sign up for
...invite code and you give us a few examples of what you'd like to use...
for and then over time will be letting in more and more developers to the service and this is really
so that we can get feedback from the developer audiences to what changes you like to see
...what's working and what's not so I'll sign-in.
now I have in mind and application that I'd like to build around being able to find
send share and read use topics and I want to be able to access this
...I want to be able to what my users interact with it the audio
so the first thing I'll do is also a new application
...news chat find share...news...news.
...create a new application forming.
And, what's create.
I can then come in and I can choose to
edit the application now with
...you'll notice on the left-hand side of the screen that there's
So, intense mapped to...a
...full sentence is in the app some application I want to be able to find news I want to be able to
share it with someone and I want to be able to read a specific item.
And, the entities in this case are the
objects we take those actions on when I go to find news...news about a topic if I want to
send it to someone I want to send it to a specific person so the first thing I'll do is I'll
define some entities so when I go to send I want to be able
And, when I go to find news...have a...topic?
Similarly we can go
up here and we can create those intense so I mentioned we have share news.
We also have find news.
Finally will have read news.
And, intent.
Clear these notifications.
And, now that I've told...you know, what actions I'd like toI'd like my model
to understand what type of entities I'm going to look to get back now we switch into this main have
...this new utterances area are you start giving...examples and you tell...you know,
this is what I'd like to handle and this is how I expect users to
interactive my application to find news about bill?
So, the first thing that I'll do when this comes up in this drop down box over here I can
pick what intend this phrase matches to
...finding news this is a find news intent and then in the phrase that I've
typed I can select any of the words or really any part of the
string I can dragon highlight and then I can say what entity this is to find use about
...the news topic so label that approximate I could try another way of asking for news
so tell me news about.
Again, I'll come over here I'll say that this is a find news example...is
...news topic and...submit this to...now I can give
some examples of other intense so share with jim.
We'll say that as a share news intent.
Jim is the recipient.
And, now one of the things that tends to be very valuable for model building is providing negative
examples something that I know that this model should never identify
within intent so just one example is what is the population seattle this
is something my news minding apple never understand so,
it's pretty labeled as none here and I can just submit.
Now you see me add a recipient
...topics I've defined two types of entities that are really important
...application but when I think about how I want the app to be able to read news so I want
users to be able to say things like read the third item so third in that case would be the way that I want to select
...item from the lest but with...we have a set of
prebuilt in entities and they're coming from...so for a lot of common use
cases we provide prebuilt entity understanding models so that you don't have to worry about
defining these yourself so everything from being able to understand
temperature the bottom here being able to understand dates and times these are things that
...comes ready to help you with is important entity for your application even something like
this encyclopedia entity identifier is preloaded with thousands of different
entities and topics locations places things like that and, this can be a massive time
saver when you're trying to build a model so I'll come back up here
and also to ordeal...how I'm going to refer to things my application so
now when I come in and I say something like read me the third item.
Similar window that you've seen before but
because I said orders are important my application is already labeled that's
...in order now so all I have to do is say, you know,
this is a read news intent...submit that.
So, now you'll notice along the bottom of the screen that looses re picked up and started training
...look you've entered in a few utterances I'm going to train a model for
you so now what happens when they come in and I say,... find news about asher.
So, in this case...with those couple of examples this is enough to get
...model built-in...and it can start trying to match these utterances no
find use about asher so it's already said look I think adders
...topic and I'm pretty sure I'm very sure that
...uses the intent.
We can get some...and we can say things like, you know,
we could say,...tell me.
About seattle.
Again, find news is labeled this intent didn't quite get entity we
label this being news topic.
So, now I've labeled a few utterances retrain the application
manually and I'm ready to start trying this out so I come back to
the my application page another's published button is available
...publish web service was happening here is
...going into taking the model that I've trained
...hosting it...and it's giving it at the endpoint that I can start...over
...over http so now I can type something like
share with john.
Little bit bigger and now you can see this is the response I get back
from my model so share news is the highest ranked
intent.
Didn't quite get the think we get the entity there but that's okay I'll show you how we can go back and
adjust that later on we can try a few more examples...with...we can say find
news about cricket now in this case lewis's predicted the intent
...find news and it's pulled out cricket as being the news topic that I'd like
to work against you can...in my application as you see this is
...news I can take this entity that is identified and I can just
operating on that directly I don't have to do a lot of extra work to try and figure
out what that entity ends up being now let me give...example of something that I'm pretty sure this
...model is not going to of generalize to yet so when I go to share thing, you know,
people might want to be able to say something like chute that to james?
...returned hasn't identified any entities here and in fact it said that the
most likely intent in this case is none...catch-all bucket that says look this doesn't seem
to match any of the other intense that you've previously define for me.
So, I will now come back to
...will close this window...come into edit.
Nouns main page if I come up to the suggestion tab so now you're going to see, you know,
all these the three utterances that I've issued against the application
...against the model
and these aren't necessarily going to be in the exact order that I've issued
...against the applicationthe reason for this is thanks active learning what
...does it orders these based on the ones that are most likely to
improve the model so the one to the top of improving the model the most if I label them
and doing this by hand here where I've labeled three or four of them ...not too hard it's very quick and easy to
...these utterances but once you've built kind of an initial model into your application you
...it with a couple of people and maybe you're getting hundreds even thousands or
tens of thousands utterances coming in a day this is one of the biggest time savers of
...so it always puts...the top the ones that are most important for you to
label to make the model better so when you have some time to go in label those
are always working on the most impactful ones so this is the same interface that...showing before so shoot
that to james I'm going to say that this is share news and also the james a recipient.
Share with john is a recipient but share news are already predicting correctly.
And, find use about cricket this was labeled correctly both in terms of the intend and
the entity so awesome at that one.
The one thing on the left-hand side that I haven't shown is model features so
model features are a way to tell us there's sort of words or there's a set of phrases that are really
important the application these are hits if you see any of these words you see any of
these phrases pay closer
attention to that to the to that word or phrase.
In this case of being able to share news and wanting to identify recipient
maybe I say look I have a set of names and names are really important...
names less and I can just take a list of names that already have.
...them in as a comma separated lest.
Into...here's a set of features you should, should really think about and,
treated stronger hands so now if I come back to
new utterances and I say something like chute that to amber.
Great share news identified as the strongest strongest
intent amber identified as the most likely
recipient.
You can even try a few more...such as find me news on office.
Find news again.
The correctly predicted intent offices not entity and we get
...you can see that over time you kind of come back and forth...you label if
you more utterances it builds a new model for you try that out...that's
doing me see what users are submitting you keep kind of updating this over and over again
whenever you want to come back to the my applications page
...publish you can update the published application and
...of a sudden shoot that to...
A and all published the update model and
it's bound share news and...as the correct recipient.
So, that's how easy it is to end up building a model with...
So, just giving these few examples that you what your application to handle giving if you
utterances ...model for you...the active learning that I talked about earlier on which
is always making the time you put into labeling the most valuable time
that it could be because it only provides the ones very provides the ones
at the top of the list that give the model the most information.
So, that's the set of services that we are announcing today for project oxford and
...show you how to get started with these ...as...a private preview all
the other services are actually available in beta starting today.
So, we switch over to a browser and
reading come to the project oxford website.
Our website you can find our demos and...documentations which we've talked about a little bit before but
let's say I'm interested in the speech api and signing up for those.
So, I come to the speech api page is
click sign up this will take me over the as your management
portal so all of our services make use of your existing measure accounts and subscriptions.
And, once this loads the marketplace we come in and we've got three
...face api entry speech entry and the vision api entry and
you'll pick that from the west.
Once you...from the west another moment here's if it comes up
...great so I can come in and I can say that I want access to
Make sure given a name to its...service and as I mentioned all of
these are available starting today in beta or providing a free
...of access for all of these that gives you five thousand transactions for each of the api
is each month so...the transaction is roughly, you know,
every rest api call counts as one transaction.
It reviews the purchase asks me whether or not
that I'm okay with it being a free purchase this is where you can find
...terms of use and privacy policy as well and once this is done...let me
purchased this and it'll show up in my list of applications so
now I can go to one that I've already.
That I've already create and once you've added this your
asher account you need to get your api token
this is how you actually you the secret key you include in your rest call so it knows that
your authorized to use it you manage all of these on our project oxford page you can
...this older one here called speech api is that I've already purchased and my primary
key and secondary key and show and you can regenerate these and,
use them as needed within your application.
So, again, to microsoft project oxford so, you know,
...collection of rest api...we're proud to announce today and,
we want this to help you developers to be able to write smarter applications
don't need to be an expert in machine learning don't need to be an expert in some of these advanced vision
and speech recognition tasks are natural language processing so,
we just help youeasily understand that content in your applications especially
...content start be more and more readily available
...carrying around one two or maybe even three devices in our pockets that's
got a video camera that's got a microphone in it so being able to unlock
what's in that is incredibly powerful task...constantly
a evolving set of services as well so I've talked about this...we're announcing today
...your feedback is going to be very important to us and figure out what are the next set of services we
launch so every requests for you so go to our website so you can
find that www dot project oxford dot ai stop
...booth we have a booth on the third-floor there we can help you get you register
...any the services we can answer questions we can get you signed up for...for
...code you can be one of the first users to make use of...very mentioned already, you know,
this is first step we...forums are come give us feedback tell us what extra features you
want to see and finally with a vision api as I only touch kind of briefly on the set of services that
...in the vision api...the features that come out of them on friday there's a talk from
the nas on the bing team and he'll be going into much more detail as what the services are?
So,...it today for our talk so kind of a final reminders
...mention in the beginning...we evaluate the session tell us how we did and, again,
stop...booth but us know what you think about project oxford and we're really
excited to see and hear what you build with these sets of services thank you.